(Sheldon:)Of course I do. The essence of the custom
is that I now have to go and purchase...
(Sheldon:)...a gift of commensurate value and
representing the same level of friendship...
(Sheldon:)...as that represented by the gift
you've given me.
(Sheldon:)It's no wonder suicide rates skyrocket
this time of year.
Okay, forget it,
I'm not giving you a present.
(Sheldon:)No, it's too late. I see it.
That elf sticker says "To Sheldon."
(Sheldon:)The die has been cast.
The moving finger has writ.
(Sheldon:)Hannibal has crossed the Alps.
(Howard(to Raj who is whispering in his ear):)I know. It's funny
when it's not happening to us.
- Sheldon, I am very, very sorry.
- No, no. I brought this on myself...
(Sheldon:)...by being such an endearing
and important part of your life.
(Sheldon:)I'm going to need a ride to the mall.
(Howard:)It's happening to us.
LEONARD:
Ow. Ow.
DAVID: Are you gonna make it?
- Yeah, I guess.
(Leonard:)Thanks for letting me try out
your motorcycle.